<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>this is bad art</title>
    <link>https://nshero.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on this is bad art</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 20:17:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nshero.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>006</title>
      <link>https://nshero.github.io/posts/006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 20:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshero.github.io/posts/006/</guid>
      <description>I was overwhelmed by the archive project, burrowing deeper and deeper without any sense of progress or perspective. I wondered: Is this whole garbage barge (GARBARGE??) moving at all? Is this accomplishing my goals? How will I know if it is or is not? What is the &amp;lsquo;goal&amp;rsquo; of a project that feels like an endless, unchartered sea? If I keep on this route how will I ever finish anything? I needed to re-find the center, or whatever felt like the closest thing to the squelchy heart of the whole endeavor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>005</title>
      <link>https://nshero.github.io/posts/005/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshero.github.io/posts/005/</guid>
      <description>I hated talking on the phone, and really the only people who called me were my parents (and spammers). So they went to voicemail. Constantly. After years of having a mother who would, on some occasions, call me upwards of four times a day, I had finally tried to set a few boundaries. Then I let them grow taller and taller. When I resolved to stop answering so many phone calls, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell if their need was increasing or if my desire for freedom and self-determination was growing, or both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>004</title>
      <link>https://nshero.github.io/posts/004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshero.github.io/posts/004/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve finally gotten around to tagging all of my old journal entries, but it&amp;rsquo;s a little more trying than I anticipated. Firstly, because I have not been very efficient. I say &amp;ldquo;efficient&amp;rdquo; less in terms of productivity and more in terms of wheel-spinning. It&amp;rsquo;s basically a &amp;ldquo;theme&amp;rdquo; of my work to take the long way round, to over-stress and over-work myself over nothing. To spend hours upon hours hunched over a tiny detail until it becomes unrecognizable but the piece as a whole has remained a stranger in the next room the whole time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>003</title>
      <link>https://nshero.github.io/posts/003/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshero.github.io/posts/003/</guid>
      <description>how it feels to collect you:
(I have been trying to reframe some of my language from &amp;ldquo;archiving&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;collecting,&amp;rdquo; as I believe that it is more accurate. Archiving implies a method of organization and an attention to certain information that I am currently disregarding.)
like a betrayal of your current self, the you who is not reading this right now, the &amp;ldquo;future you&amp;rdquo; to whom you wrote as a despairing high school sophomore like re-committing my love to you, both in the past and in the present like delaying our reunion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>002</title>
      <link>https://nshero.github.io/posts/002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 10:19:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshero.github.io/posts/002/</guid>
      <description>Here are two elusive things.
In 1996-1997, I was taught a primary-level cross-disciplinary curriculum for &amp;ldquo;gifted&amp;rdquo; (cringe) students in a small pull-out program. The curriculum implements a frame story that may involve several children traveling to a distant land (it may have been another country, or perhaps an imaginary dimension) and meeting a girl named Zara who wore a Claddagh ring. The program included an audio-cassette reading of the story and several accompanying songs, which may have centered around common aphorisms like &amp;ldquo;look before you leap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>001</title>
      <link>https://nshero.github.io/posts/001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 10:23:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshero.github.io/posts/001/</guid>
      <description>Now when I think of making something new I also think about having to preserve it. Might as well get it saved away ahead of time so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to yank its guts out of another wayback scrape.
It adds an extra weight to whatever I start, which is a hindrance.
What is worth keeping? What is okay to throw away? Despite a year and a half of ferreting around, I haven&amp;rsquo;t come to any answer at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>https://nshero.github.io/projects/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshero.github.io/projects/overview/</guid>
      <description>Research
Archives Archive as a narrative tool and a form of surveillance; the concept of curation as control. Archive as an art form or framing device; examples of fictional archives or creative cataloging Practical archiving concepts and skills – software, cataloging, and preservation techniques Context Web 1.0, theories of World Wide Web connectivity, data/knowledge-sharing concepts (The Medium is the Message) Online communities, particularly relating to moderation, cohesiveness as a function of size, and personal identity formation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>