<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>this is bad art</title>
    <link>https://nshero.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on this is bad art</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 10:19:19 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nshero.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>002</title>
      <link>https://nshero.github.io/posts/002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 10:19:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshero.github.io/posts/002/</guid>
      <description>Here are two elusive things.
In 1996-1997, I was taught a primary-level cross-disciplinary curriculum for &amp;ldquo;gifted&amp;rdquo; (cringe) students in a small pull-out program. The curriculum implements a frame story that may involve several children traveling to a distant land (it may have been another country, or perhaps an imaginary dimension) and meeting a girl named Zara who wore a Claddagh ring. The program included an audio-cassette reading of the story and several accompanying songs, which may have centered around common aphorisms like &amp;ldquo;look before you leap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>001</title>
      <link>https://nshero.github.io/posts/001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 10:23:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshero.github.io/posts/001/</guid>
      <description>Now when I think of making something new I also think about having to preserve it. Might as well get it saved away ahead of time so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to yank its guts out of another wayback scrape.
It adds an extra weight to whatever I start, which is a hindrance.
What is worth keeping? What is okay to throw away? Despite a year and a half of ferreting around, I haven&amp;rsquo;t come to any answer at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>https://nshero.github.io/projects/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshero.github.io/projects/overview/</guid>
      <description>Research
Archives Archive as a narrative tool and a form of surveillance; the concept of curation as control. Archive as an art form or framing device; examples of fictional archives or creative cataloging Practical archiving concepts and skills – software, cataloging, and preservation techniques Context Web 1.0, theories of World Wide Web connectivity, data/knowledge-sharing concepts (The Medium is the Message) Online communities, particularly relating to moderation, cohesiveness as a function of size, and personal identity formation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>